Kyung Haug

(206) 990-3312 kyung.haug@outlook.com linkedin.com/in/kyung-haug github.com/kyungh Kirkland, WA

Newly transitioned Air Force veteran with over 6 years of professional and technical experience with .NET/C# experience through the Microsoft Software & Systems Academy apprenticeship seeking a role as a software engineer.

PROJECTS

03/2021	Mortgage Calculator - C#
	 Developed C#-based forms app that calculates user's monthly payments and total cost for a potential home over the loan period.
01/2021	Let's Learn Japanese! - C#
	• Created WPF application that shows ENG/JPN translations for basic words.
EXPERIENCE	
01/2021 - Present	Cloud App Developer, Microsoft Software & Systems Academy – Lacey, WA
	 Demonstrated fluency in the technologies implementing .NET using Visual Studio, C#, Python, SQL, JSON, XAML, and ASP.NET, completing over 20 individual and team-based projects on various console, GUI, and cloud- based web applications.
01/2021 - Present	Network Engineer, Air National Guard - Tacoma, WA
	 Answer support tickets through a Virtual Service Desk via phone consultations, emails, and site visits that peaked customer satisfaction at 95%, 5% over organization's goal.
08/2017 - 01/2021	Data Analyst, U.S. Air Force – Okinawa, Japan
	 Provided 15 high-priority trend analysis to 2 internal departments that saved \$300K+ in mechanical repairs.

EDUCATION

05/2021	Certificate, Computer Science, Saint Martin's University
10/2020	Certificate, MTA 98-361: Software Development Fundamentals, Microsoft
08/2020	Bachelor of Arts (BA), Asian Studies, Univ. of Maryland: Global Campus
08/2020	Certificate, Japanese Studies, Univ. of Maryland: Global Campus
SKILLS	

Frontline supervisor for a six-member team that designed a new local database to increase production efficiency and reduced over 400+ man-

- C#
- ASP.NET | MVC

- HTML | CSS | JavaScript
- T-SQL | SQL Server
- Object Oriented Programming
- 1 3QL | 3QL 3CI (

hours of maintenance actions.

Python

- Microsoft Excel
- SharePoint
- Azure

LANGUAGES

English (Native)

- Japanese (Intermediate)
- Korean (Basic)